<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on InnoMx | Pharmacometric Solutions</title><link>http://innomx.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on InnoMx | Pharmacometric Solutions</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://innomx.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Strategic Consulting</title><link>http://innomx.com/services/strategic_consulting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>http://innomx.com/services/strategic_consulting/</guid><description>We start by understanding your needs. Whether you are planning a Phase 2 study, preparing for an End of Phase 2 meeting, working on your Module 2.7.2, or getting ready to submit your NDA or BLA, we can help you to ask the right questions, interrogate your data and make model-informed decisions that will increase your success rate.</description></item><item><title>Modeling &amp; Simulation</title><link>http://innomx.com/services/modeling_simulation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>http://innomx.com/services/modeling_simulation/</guid><description>This is the crux of what we do: population PK, PK/PD and exposure-response modeling. A good population PK model is a cornerstone for understanding your drug&amp;rsquo;s exposure-efficacy and exposure-safety profile. Once a model has been estblished, simulations are an invaluable tool for making predictions (what-if scenarios), designing new trial, and optimizing dosing in special populations like pediatrics.</description></item><item><title>Interactive Apps</title><link>http://innomx.com/services/interactive_apps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>http://innomx.com/services/interactive_apps/</guid><description>Interactive Shiny apps have taken the pharmacometrics world by storm, and with good reason.</description></item><item><title>Custom Coding</title><link>http://innomx.com/services/custom_coding/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>http://innomx.com/services/custom_coding/</guid><description>We can help to improve the efficiency of your pharmacometric workflows with custom code libraries and R packages.</description></item><item><title>Due Diligence</title><link>http://innomx.com/services/due_diligence/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>http://innomx.com/services/due_diligence/</guid><description>How confident are you in your population PK or PK/PD model? Will it stand up to the scrutiny of regulatory agencies? It is always best to have a second, unbiased opinion, which we can provide. We will push, prod and pressure test your model to uncover any potential weaknesses, and propose solutions to address them. Having this information up front can be invaluable, and well worth a small investment to avoid the consequences of uncovering it later on in the submission process.</description></item><item><title>Training</title><link>http://innomx.com/services/training/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>http://innomx.com/services/training/</guid><description>We provide training courses in R, Pumas, and NONMEM.</description></item></channel></rss>